valuenotes.com 2007-12-11

# Privacy Policy

|   
---  
   
|     
---  
  
**[Publish your Research](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/services/publish.asp)** or thoughts on the Indian stock markets on ValueNotes... The platform for stock brokers, writers, analysts, investors…   

|  **PRIVACY POLICY** When you subscribe to any paid or free service of ValueNotes, you need to give us some basic contact information such as your full name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, etc. We also ask for demographic information, which helps us understand our audience so that we can continue to provide appropriate content. From time to time, we may request your input in order to evaluate potential features and services for ValueNotes or its partners. We might invite you to participate in a survey that is posted on the web or we may e-mail a survey to you. Answering them is completely voluntary. 

**Will we disclose your personal information to outside parties?**   
ValueNotes does not rent, sell, or share personal information with other people or non-affiliated companies, except to provide products or services you've requested for. We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of, or with, ValueNotes under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help ValueNotes communicate with you about offers from ValueNotes We analyse statistical information gathered through our registrations in order to make ValueNotes a more valuable product for our subscribers and visitors. From time to time, we share this information in aggregate with a third party. However, this data is reported only in aggregate and reveals no personal details about individual visitors to our site. This information is used only to help attract appropriate advertisers for the ValueNotes site. 

**In short**  
ValueNotes is committed to protecting your privacy. Personal information that we collect about you stays within ValueNotes, unless we have your permission. And any information distributed to third parties is reported in aggregate only. We do not give or sell your information to people who want to send you spam e-mails.

|   
---  
About ValueNotes :: [About ValueNotes ](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/aboutus/default.asp)|| [VN Outsourcing Practice](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/aboutus/outsourcing.asp) || [Business intelligence & Research ](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/aboutus/business.asp)|| About ValueNotes.com || [Careers ](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/aboutus/careers.asp)|| [Contact Us ](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/aboutus/contact.asp)  
Research :: [Companies](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/research/company.asp) || [Industries ](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/research/industry.asp) || [Commodities ](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/research/commodity.asp)|| [Mutualfunds ](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/research/mutualfund.asp)|| [Policy ](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/research/govtpolicy.asp)|| [Economy ](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/research/economy.asp)|| [MarkeTalk ](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/research/markettalk.asp)|| [TaxOLegal ](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/research/tax.asp)  
Learning Centre :: [Equity Investment ](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/learning/equity.asp)|| [Personal Finance](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/learning/personal.asp)  
Contributors' Corner :: [Technical ](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/contributor/contributor.asp?cap=1)|| [Fundamental](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/contributor/contributor.asp?cap=2) || [Post Market Analysis ](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/contributor/contributor.asp?cap=3)|| Contribute  
Services/ Products :: [Publish ](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/services/publish.asp)|| [Sell](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/services/sell.asp) || [Inform ](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/services/inform.asp)|| [Advertise ](http://www.valuenotes.com/valuenotes/services/advertise.asp)|| Research Reports || Subscription Products  
Forum :: [Forum](http://www.valuenotes.com/forum/default.asp)  
  |
